{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Rodent Control Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40106/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40106,"taskName":"Pest Control - Rodents","taskDescription":"Control or Eliminate Rodents","xmTaskDescriptor":"Rodent Control Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":4713,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Control Pest exterminator mice rats","textMessagingName":"Pest Control Rodent","rolloverLongDesc":"Extermination, nest removal, animal control, etc.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes rats, mice, snakes.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Control or Eliminate Rodents.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Rodent Control \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Rat \u0026 Mice Control Services","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":58,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Rodent Control","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Pest Control - Rodents","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Pest Control Project","urlName":"Pest-Control-Rodents","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Rodent Control Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Rat \u0026 Mice Control","searchKeywords":"Control,Pest,exterminate,mice,rats,pesticide,exterminators,Rodents, mouse, squirrel, raccoon","emcCategoryOid":-12057,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":417,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564376531963pwspr010F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40106/":{"taskOID":40106,"originalTaskOID":40106,"setID":417,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4391,"questionDisplayText":"Rodent Types","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of rodents do you need controlled?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5040,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Rats","answerDisplayText":"Rats","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3832,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mice","answerDisplayText":"Mice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3906,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Moles","answerDisplayText":"Moles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8981,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other Rodents","answerDisplayText":"Other Rodents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1229,"questionDisplayText":"Specific Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the specific rodent control problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202087,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior damage","answerDisplayText":"Exterior damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2275,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Excessive noise","answerDisplayText":"Excessive noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5373,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Rodent waste","answerDisplayText":"Rodent waste","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4125,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Nesting","answerDisplayText":"Nesting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1824,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dangerous rodents","answerDisplayText":"Dangerous rodents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4331,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Odor","answerDisplayText":"Odor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2944,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Health concerns","answerDisplayText":"Health concerns","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2827,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Gnawing electrical wiring","answerDisplayText":"Gnawing electrical wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1811,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Damaged ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Damaged ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":60001,"questionDisplayText":"Recurring Service Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will this request be a recurring service?","shortQuestionText":"Is a recurring service?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4391,"questionDisplayText":"Rodent Types","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of rodents do you need controlled?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5040,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Rats","answerDisplayText":"Rats","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3832,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mice","answerDisplayText":"Mice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3906,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Moles","answerDisplayText":"Moles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8981,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other Rodents","answerDisplayText":"Other Rodents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5040,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Rats","answerDisplayText":"Rats","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3832,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mice","answerDisplayText":"Mice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3906,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Moles","answerDisplayText":"Moles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8981,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other Rodents","answerDisplayText":"Other Rodents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1229,"questionDisplayText":"Specific Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the specific rodent control problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202087,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior damage","answerDisplayText":"Exterior damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2275,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Excessive noise","answerDisplayText":"Excessive noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5373,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Rodent waste","answerDisplayText":"Rodent waste","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4125,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Nesting","answerDisplayText":"Nesting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1824,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dangerous rodents","answerDisplayText":"Dangerous rodents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4331,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Odor","answerDisplayText":"Odor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2944,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Health concerns","answerDisplayText":"Health concerns","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2827,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Gnawing electrical wiring","answerDisplayText":"Gnawing electrical wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1811,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Damaged ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Damaged ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":202087,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior damage","answerDisplayText":"Exterior damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2275,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Excessive noise","answerDisplayText":"Excessive noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5373,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Rodent waste","answerDisplayText":"Rodent waste","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4125,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Nesting","answerDisplayText":"Nesting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1824,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dangerous rodents","answerDisplayText":"Dangerous rodents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4331,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Odor","answerDisplayText":"Odor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2944,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Health concerns","answerDisplayText":"Health concerns","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2827,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Gnawing electrical wiring","answerDisplayText":"Gnawing electrical wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1811,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Damaged ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Damaged ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":60001,"questionDisplayText":"Recurring Service Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will this request be a recurring service?","shortQuestionText":"Is a recurring service?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}